



## **ABOUT ME**

I have worked as a cinematographer for over 15 years, within film and television production. In 2021 I decided to start studying frontend design. Today I am studying UX/UI with Frontend competence at Chas Academy. Combining my creative experience with photography and design with web design is extremely exciting. Running my own company as a freelancer has taught me how to communicate with clients, lead teams and to work multiple projects under pressure. Growing up in the UK I moved to Sweden in 2001 I am fluent in both English and Swedish.

## **CARACTERISTICS**

## **SKILLS AND TOOLS**

Calm • Methodical • Willpower • Positive • Social • Entreprenurial • Action oriented • Creative

html • css • javascript • jQuery • jQuery animation • Studio Visual Code • Adobe Photoshop • Adobe Lightroom • Design

## **EXPERIENCE**

2022 Student@ChasAcademy, UX/UI Frontend Stockholm

2006 to date Cinematographer, freelance Stockholm

#### **Latest TV Projects**

Streams S2, Tv Series, SVT 2021 Vi Forever, Tv Series, SVT 2020 Last Journey of the Vikings, TV Series, Viaplay, 2019

### **Selected Commercial projects**

FLX - Fonus, Barncancerfonden, Renault, Forex
Fanny & Alexander Productions AB - Call of Duty
Savvy Pictures - Coop med Lotta Lundgren,
Made To Order - Stadium, Gant
Milford Film Studios - Fruit-Tella, Westlands safe lawn, FTPE UK, IKEA
Indio - Sony Xperia
Flodell Film - Gröna Lund, Boxer, Volvo, Stryktipset, Triss, Honda, Lambi
B-Reel - Doritos Hotel 626, Statoil
Ligist Film - Lloyds Apotek, Burger King, ICA MAXI, IVT

**2002-2006 Forsberg och Co,** Full-time. camera assistant

Stockholm

## **EDUCATION**

2022-To date	PHP for beginners Udemy	Digitalt
2021-2022	Frontend Developer ChangeMaker Education	Stockholm, Swe
2021-2021	Programmering 1 Jensen Komvux	Stockholm, Swe
1997-1999	Bournemouth Film School Higher National Diploma, Film och Television	Bournemouth, UK
1995-1997	Alton College A-levels, Design Technology och Communication	Alton, UK

# **ACTIVITES AND INTERESTS**

Surfing • Running • Gym • Traveling • Family and Friends • Food • Film • Photography